This is such a drag,
first thing in the morning.
What a brat! Stop complaining
and get to work, Knight!
That's that chick from the other day...
I think her name was "Meguru."
Who's the other kid?
He must be another Prime Right owner...
Whaddya think, Raion?
Should we attack?
No, it'd be best if we can gather
information without taking them head-on.
We'll listen in on their conversation for now.
I don't want them messing
with Sane's body.
If they make their way inside
the tower, we're attacking.
Good?
Okay.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Jeez! It's so tall!
Hey, you said you went to the top, right?
Can't you teleport there
with your Exchange Right?
It's way too far from down here.
Exchange Right!
So that's Meguru's Prime Right!
Judging from what they just said,
there must be other conditions to use it.
Aw man!
We can't get in 'cause of the rubble!
Ikusa blew a hole in it before.
It piled up again?
So annoying.
Oh well. Knight, it's all yours.
Raion!
Yeah!
If I have to!
Prime Right of—
Knight!
I missed!
Mommy! I-I-I-I was so scared!
It's the guy from KHN!
You'll have to deal with me!
It's the Rejection Right kid.
Lady Kisaragi warned me about his tactic:
using the Response Right
followed by the Rejection Right...
That's all the information I need
to deal with you!
He must have forgotten my Prime Right.
I'll make sure you take
each other down this time!
Prime Right of...
Exchange!
It's not working?!
Checkmate.
You're already under the command
of my Prime Right of Control.
Control?!
Once I activate my Control Right,
all those within my reach will
lose their Prime Right abilities.
And unless I release my control,
anyone I touch who tries
to use their Rights will... die!
It adds up...
I had no problem using my Exchange Right
before I came to Hibiya.
But now...
The Rejection Right hasn't
even been used on me, yet...
It was the Control Right...
I'm in trouble!
Of course I'm lying, you idiot!
The reason you can't use your Exchange
Right is the Rejection Right.
Once the Rejection Right is activated,
the effects last for 72 hours.
72 Hours
It's only been two and a half days
since our last battle.
Which means the Rejection Right
still stands for now.
All I needed to do was inform her
that she can't use the Exchange Right,
and this little act about my so-called
"Control Right" gets eaten right up.
I even tacked on a restriction by
threatening death if she uses her Right.
A perfect plan to neutralize Meguru's powers.
All that's left is...
Hey, you! That was scary as hell!
What was that for?! Stop it, will ya?!
Man, you're really just a kid.
Fine, then hurry up and scram home!
Just to get yelled at by the hag?!
No way!
"Hag"? You mean the Queen?
That's how you guys treat your Queen?
It's the death sentence for you!
What the—
Destruction Right
Prime Right of Destruction!
Go ahead and beat me if you can!
Destruction?!
What kind of pure violence
is that for a Right?!
Destruction Right?
You think Ryuta will be okay?
Ryuta-kun is even stronger now
thanks to his training in Tohoku, but...
The Fusion Right is the power
to uniquely control fusion,
reconstruction, and separation...
If he fuses with a building,
that building becomes a part
of his body for his full control.
He can even fuse with the ground to control
the earth, at least within a certain scope.
But that's exactly
why it would lose all power
if substances themselves
get physically destroyed.
Destruction Right versus Fusion Right...
There couldn't be a worse match!
Fuse!
He fused with the ground
to take away his footing!
Perfect!
You can't physically destroy
anything if you're free falling!
Take that!
Right of... Flight!
Flight Right
He flew?!
Thought you got me?!
I don't think so!
Aww, don't you have a comeback like before?
Don't tell me you're scared!
Looks like Ryuta's figured out
the bad match-up...
If we could at least catch the kid...
There's no point in restraining him
without taking away his Rights.
I was able to stop Meguru by bluffing, but...
I might blow my cover about
the Control Right if I get involved...
Maybe if we used the Rejection Right...
No, that won't work!
Damn it... Think!
There's gotta be a way!
If you won't make a move, I will.
I'll destroy everything!
Take this!
Crap! I can't dodge all that!
Ryuta-kun!
Wh-What was that?!
Gotcha! Nailed every blow!
I didn't expect the Queen
to recruit children, of all people.
What's going on?
Now, what next?
Time for this kid to learn a lesson!
This is quite the trouble already...
Prime Right of Obtainment.
Prime Right of...
Induction!
Destruction Field!
Hmm... A new application
of the Destruction Right?
Interesting. But...
It stopped?
I used my Suspension Right on the rock
to suspend time within a
one-meter radius when it crumbles.
Victory is ours!
Wow...
They won in no time...
Yagi-chan! Sudocchi!
But why?! How?!
I have no clue how this is possible!
And besides... besides!
Ippy-hiko!
Knight lost...
And I can't use my Prime Right anymore.
Does that woman over there serve the Queen?
Huh? Yeah...
I see.
Okay then, you can take
that child and go home now.
What?!
Hang on! We need her for info—
Are you a new member?
Don't worry about it and let them go.
It's for the best. You'll know soon enough.
Yeah, Raion.
I promise we'll be fine as long
as we listen to Sudocchi.
Mm-yup.
Okay.
You heard them.
Take the kid and get outta here.
I'll deactivate my Control Right
once I know you're far enough away.
M'kay then!
We're following them, right?!
Let's go!
Absolutely not.
What?!
Yo, where have you been
all this time anyway?!
Right, sorry about that. You see...
Catch ya later, Saneatsu. Everyone.
Prime Right under the Production Attribute...
Explosion Right!
Huh?
Where am I?
Wait, am I...
I'm... alive?
Why am I alive?
I guess I never saw myself dying, so...
I must have never died?
But I definitely blew up... huh?
Wait, now that I think of it
I don't remember that either...
Guess I'll never know!
Reached cognitive limit
Let's just assess the situation!
Food!
First thing's first, I need to eat!
Forget That Other Stuff
You must be hungry.
Here, have some.
Nice! Thanks!
Wait, what?
Pres?!
So it was Pres who helped me out?!
Sure, I suppose I did.
H-How?
We have plenty of time. Go ahead and eat.
I actually have two Rights:
Suspension Right
The Right of Suspension
and the Prime Right of Induction.
Induction Right
I used both of them to help you.
Huh? I don't remember you having any Rights.
Perhaps I should explain from the beginning.
First off, the Suspension Right...
On Day 2 of Tasuketsu, I found it when
I was revived in the school nurse's room.
Right
That long ago?!
This Right actually turned out
to be very powerful.
It can stop certain phenomena
within designated subjects.
Including things like time.
What?! That's so crazy!
You'd think so, right?
But this is just a Right.
So I tested some scenarios,
and found that it actually had
quite a few restrictions...
Activations limited to four at a time
Restriction #1: Activations
are limited to four at a time.
Restriction #2: Time designations.
I need to designate conditions
and set them beforehand to activate.
Restriction #3: It only holds effect if I'm
within a one-meter radius from the subject.
Man... that sounds really inconveniet.
It really is.
I had an idea of how I could use it,
but I decided not to tell you guys so
I could focus on supporting everyone.
And later, I obtained
the Prime Right of Induction,
or the ability to physically direct
the line of flow of things.
Physically direct... lines and flow...?
Physically direct lines and flow
I'm not sure what that means, but...
How exactly were you able to save me?
I set the Suspension Right on you.
It seemed to me that you were
planning on trying something reckless,
so I designated the Right to activate
when your life was put in danger.
When you were engulfed in the explosion,
the Suspension Right went into effect
and everything within a one-meter radius
of your body stopped in time for a moment.
So that's how my life was saved!
Hey, guys?
The Suspension Right is incredible!
Can you, like, fly with the Induction Right?!
Man... this kind of treatment...
Feels good to be back, guys...
This spacey dude named Ippy-hiko
can act as a striker-type position...
As for the other two...
Wait a second!
The Suspension Right can be used
for four events at a time, so...
Cool, then let's head back
to our headquarters.
No, we'll head somewhere
we've prepared beforehand.
We'll use Souma's Materialization Right
to prepare a few devices.
Bring Eren Kunashiri and Shuji Nihonyanagi.
I'll tell you where to go.
Shuji Nihonyanagi?
Nishime, remember?
They must already have a plan in place...
Man, we were a bit lost without
a strategist, but no worries now.
So then, these guys really
were the ones who...
Yup! These guys were the brains
who led us to the Emperor...
and they're back!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Sudo Senpai, you really were alive...
Sudo...
There's a reason why I gathered you all here,
but I'm sure you have some questions.
Let's get that over with.
Sudo...
How?
That day, I'm certain I checked
to see if your heart stopped...
To cut to the chase, I never died.
Yagihashi's Suspension Right
put me in a similar state,
and I was waiting for
my opportunity of revival.
I set it to halt time when he came
face-to-face with impending death
but could still recover with 100% certainty.
But I never knew that
you had any Rights, Pres.
Well sure, I kept it a secret!
I found it at school, in the nurse's
room on Day 2 of Tasuketsu.
But he was so prepared to die in the name
of defeating the Emperor that I...
He was insistent that
I protect myself, just in case!
I had a hard time finding Sudo-kun...
After all, he was buried in the yard
of a school I'd never seen before.
Once I found a doctor, I deactivated
the Suspension Right and had him treated.
They make it sound so easy,
but this is really advanced stuff.
I see...
Thank goodness...
Huh? Hang on...
Mm-yup?
Our school is in Suginami Ward.
Wasn't Nerima the Designated Area for Day 2?
I thought envelopes were only placed within
that day's Designated Area.
Oh yeah...
They were recovered
by the Emperor at midnight.
Good thinking, but you already hold
the answer to that question, Kunashiri.
What?
When and where did you get your own Right?
When and where...?
Saneatsu found the envelope on Day 1...
which I opened on Day 2!
Exactly.
Once envelopes are obtained by someone,
they can't be recovered at the time limit.
In other words, the Suspension Right
Yagihashi obtained
were once obtained by someone
else, and left unopened.
That being said, who knows if it was
something that just happened to be there,
or if it was placed there
by someone on purpose.
Now, let's get to the main topic.
I want everyone to take a look at this.
Who is that?!
This is one of the Queen's members,
whom Kazuhiko-kun and I captured.
The Queen's?!
One of her members?
Wow, for real...
He's actually suspended in time
right now, thanks to my Right,
but I'm going to deactivate it so he can
tell us everything about their group.
These guys...
While we were flailing around,
barely getting by,
they'd already gotten this far?!
Now... First up, Nishime-kun.
Y-Yes!
I'd like for you to use your Priority Right
to prioritize Kunashiri-san's order.
Can you do that?
Huh?
U-Um, yeah, sure...
Great, so I'll just use my
Obedience Right to make him talk.
Actually, I'd prefer you tell him
we have some questions,
and that he can answer with either "yes" or "no."
Roger that!
Now for Jin-kun...
Mm-yup, I gotcha.
Ready? Deactivate Suspension Right.
Wh-Where am I?
Who are they?!
Could they be the current
Emperor's servants?!
I see... So I've been captured...
Then I'll—
It's no use.
I can't use my Prime Right?!
I'm neutralizing your
Prime Right... understand?
Don't pull any stunts.
Listen to us, and we'll let you go.
We're going to ask you some questions,
so answer with either "yes" or "no".
Prioritize her order...
I'm being interrogated.
I've gotta try and get by
without revealing information...
You understand your current
situation, don't you?
Yes.
Then, could ya answer
honestly to my question?
N—
This must be... the Response Right
Lady Kisaragi was talking about!
It's too powerful...
They're combining multiple Rights
to enforce their orders!
Don't you... underestimate my loyalty!
I won't let... a few Rights
win against my conviction!
How impressive.
We combined three Rights under the Permission
Attribute, and he's still able to resist.
He has incredible willpower.
Not to mention, you answered
my questions without hesitation,
but resisted here, which means...
You realized that was the Response Right,
and you're aware that
the Rejection Right is next...
Is that right?
The Rejection Right is a Prime Right.
There's no way to resist
through sheer will.
If the Rejection Right held
the power to enforce responses,
you'd know resistance is futile.
But you resisted immediately,
without hesitation.
So you already knew that the Rejection Right
and Response Right were separate.
I wonder how he knows about
the Rights of others so accurately...
Curious, indeed.
Hey! What now?!
Jin-kun, could you ask
the same question again?
Mm-yup?
My Prime Right of Induction can be
used to control movements.
His willpower is irrelevant.
Allow me to move his body
and make him say "no".
Holy crap... They gathered all that
from such a short interaction...
And his method of making him
move his body to say "no"...
That must have been the plan all along.
Combining the Rights
was just an experiment...
Yagihashi and Sudo... What a crazy duo.
All set.
So what's your name?
Touya Mutsuki...
What Rights do you own?
The Prime Right of Gravity
and Right of Hearing.
Are you one of the Queen's members?
I am.
Awesome! We'll be able to
get answers in no time!
This is a dire situation...
I can't use my Rights,
nor commit suicide, nor stay silent!
There's no way to avoid responding...
The Queen's name is Kisaragi, right?
Is she female?
Queen Kisaragi is a woman.
What to ask?
The first thing is location...
then it's their organizational
structure and members,
every member's Rights, and
I can't forget their motive...
Take it easy.
Yagihashi is asking the questions now.
There's plenty of time. Don't get hasty.
Time for the next question.
Your headquarters is in Saitama...
And the Queen's name is...
Maria Kisaragi...
Is that right?
Interrogation